Mss.B.C55
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Slater, Robert J
  - Slater, Sir William
  - Smetana, Hans
  - Smiles, Samuel, 1926-1934
    Box 7 15 items, 1926-1934. General correspondence.
  - Smith, Arthur Calvert
  - Smith, Carleton Sprague
  - Sperry, Warren M, 1965
    Box 7 1 items, 1965. Reminiscences about Rochester University Medical School by Sperry, 17 pp., 1965.
  - Sprinson, David B
  - Staley, A. E. Mfg. Co.
    Langlois, David P.
  - Stamp, Lord Garven
  - Stanley, Wendell Meredith, 1904-
  - Stanton, Madeline
  - Stavely, Homer E
  - Stein, William H
  - Stern, Joseph R
  - Sterner, James H
  - Stetten, Dewitt
    See also: Dobzhansky, Theodosius G., in: See also: Adelphi University, in:
    Hartman, W. W.
  - Stewart, Alfred Walter, 1926-1935
    Separated Materials note
    Box 7 c. 30 items, 1926-1935. General correspondence, re: political situation in N. Ireland. References to Clarke's work on non-flammable films at Kodak. Congratulations on Clarke's being appointed to Columbia, 1928. Mention of internal argumetns over appropriations to the new Dept. of Chemistry at the University of Belfast. Mention of N. Collie's retirement from University College, London. Letters in which Stewart bemoans the state of science, 1930. Advice to Clarke on how to run one's own department at a university.
  - Stotz, Elmer H
  - Stumpf, Karl
  - Such, Mrs. Doris
  - Sunderman, F William, 1960
    Box 7 8 items, 1960. General correspondence.
  - Switzer, Mary, 1967
    Box 7 2 items, 1967. Reports from the U.S. Dept. of Health, Education and Welfare on newly proposed social and rehabilitation services.
  - Tatum, Edward Lawrie, 1909-
    See also: American Chemical Society, in:
  - Taylor, Geoffrey, 1955-1972
    Box 7 c. 30, 1955-1972. Personal correspondence.
  - Tennessee Eastman Corp.
    Straley, J. M.
  - Theorell, Hugo
    See also: Nobel Prize - N - Nobel Award, in:
  - Thin, Jean
  - Thomas, Karl
    See also: Photographs, in:
  - Tippo, Oswald
  - Tishler, Max, 1966, 1970
    See also: Merck Fellowships, in: See also: Nobel Prize - T, in:
    Box 7 2 items, 1966, 1970.
  - Tobacco Industry Research Committee
    Gottschall, G. Y.; Hoyt, W. T.; Hockett, R. C.
  - Todd, Alexander, R
  - Travers, Morris W
    Box 7 1 item Article "William Ramsay in America."
  - Tuve, Merle Anthony, 1901-
    Clarke, Hans T. Bibliography; Clarke, Hans T. Biographical Sketch; Clarke, Hans T. Photograph
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization #1, 1957-1958
    McCullough, Max; Berding, Andrew H.; Wilkinson, James R.; Attwood, Wallace W.
    Box 7 2 files, 1957-1958. Correspondence, re: the 14th meeting of the UNESCO Committee on Science, March 1957.
  - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization #
    McCullough, Max; Attwood, Wallace; Richards, John R.; Obermayer, Leon L.
  - U.S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare., 1958
    Cantrell, Mrs. Catherine E.; Scantlebury, Ronald E.
    Box 7 4 items, 1958. Letters, re: grant application from Paul Zamenhof.
  - U. S. Department of State
    Farinholt, L. H.; Ziondrore, Christine.
  - University of London
  - University of Miami
    Lewis, George T.; Dietrich, Leroy L.
  - University of Rajasthan, 1962
    Box 6 15 items, 1962. Letters, re: Clarke's review of thesis of Mr. N.A. Rao.
  - Unknown (A-B)
    Box 7 7 files, Miscellaneous. Mostly personal letters from unidentified authors.
  - Unknown (C-F)
  - Unknown (G-J)
  - Unknown (J-L)
  - Unknown (M)
  - Unknown (N-P)
  - Unknown (Q-Z)
  - Van Slyke, Donald D
  - Verry, H L
  - Vogel, Henry J
  - Volwiler, E H
  - Vossius, Dorothea
    Samaras, Nicholas T.; Vossius, Volker.
  - Voznick, E L
  - Wardlaw, W
  - Ward's Natural Science Establishment
  - Watson, H E
  - Weaver, Mrs. Elizabeth
  - Weaver, Warren, 1962
    Box 7 1 item, 1962. re: election of H. Fairbank to the Century Association.
  - Weber, Annemarie
  - Webster, Michael
  - Weinberg, Barbara
  - Weiss, Adolph
  - Weissman, David
  - Werber, Frank X
  - Werth, Hans
    Werth, Elschen
  - Whitfield, Ernest
  - White, M P
  - Whiting, Arthur
  - Williams, Gwyn
  - Wintersteiner, Oskar
  - Wittenberg, Jonathan
  - Wizinger, R
  - Wood, Sydney Herbert
    Wood, Frances
  - The Work of the Medallist, 1945
    Crowe, James M.; Du Vigneaud
    Box 7 Paper give by Clarke at a meeting of the N.Y. Section of the A.C.S., March 1945, on being asked to award Vincent duVignaud the Nichols medal.
  - Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine, 1958, 1963
  - Yale Medical Library
  - Yale University
    Richards, Frederic M.
  - Yerkes, Roberta
  - Young, Leslie
  - Zaritzky, Joyce S
  - Zelitch, Israel
  - Zervas, Leonidas
  - Zimmerle, William F
  - Zinsser, Hans, 1963
    Century Association; Sanger, Grant; Zinsser, Frederick T.
    Box 7 1 items, 1963. re: being recommended to the Century Association.